(
"ai_sub_version": "2.8.2",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"ollama_search": (
"key": "**********"
),
"web_search_tool": "ollama",
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
WHERE EMOTIONS BLOOM
RAORA PANTHERA BIRTHDAY LIVE 2026
#RaoraBday2026
[Title: Where Emotions Bloom
Raora Panthera Birthday Live 2026
#RaoraBday2026]
TODAY...
[Title: Today...]
5/11 2026 RAORA'S BIRTHDAY
- Chattini, let's celebrate together! -
[Title: 5/11 2026 Raora's Birthday
- Chattini, let's celebrate together! -]
BEGINS
[Title: Begins]
WHERE EMOTIONS BLOOM
RAORA PANTHERA BIRTHDAY LIVE 2026
[Title: Where Emotions Bloom
Raora Panthera Birthday Live 2026]
Oh my god, that was a good nap.
Wait...
Wait a minute. That's not my room.
Why... why am I not at home right now?
How did I end up here?
What... white canvas? Huh?
What is this? Why is there a white canvas in here?
Heh? Where... where is my room?
Chatino!
Ah, thank God you're here.
Ah, this place is so scary, Chatino! Where are we?
Chatino... Cha...
Chatino!
Oh, what happened to you?
Ah, come here. Don't worry, I got you.
You are kind of heavy though.
Don't worry Chatino, I got you.
We need to find a way out, okay?
We're gonna find a way out.
Ah... where should we go?
Heh? Why is there a portal now?
Did you open it?
No?
Fine, I guess we should go in there.
Maybe I'm gonna wake up.
Maybe I'm still dreaming.
Issho! Let's go.
Here we go! Let's go.
You are kind of heavy though.
Issho!
Here we go!
ローリンガール
Lyrics, Music: wowaka
[Song: Rolling Girl
Lyrics, Music: wowaka]
ロンリーガールはいつまでも
For lonely girls, it's always the same,
届かない夢見て
Dreaming dreams that don't come true
騒ぐ頭の中を
And churning, churning
掻き回して、掻き回して。
Through the clamor in their heads
「問題ない。」と呟いて、
A lonely girl mutters "I'm fine",
言葉は失われた？
Have words failed her?
もう失敗、もう失敗。
A failure, a failure.
間違い探しに終われば、
Obsessing over her mistakes
また、回るの！
Makes everything spin again!
もう一回、もう一回。
One more time, one more time
「私は今日も転がります。」と、
“I'll roll along today”
少女は言う 少女は言う
The girl said, the girl said
言葉に意味を奏でながら！
Breathing life into the words!
「もう良いかい？」
“How about now?”
「まだですよ、
“Not yet,
まだまだ先は見えないので。
We still can't see what's ahead.
息を止めるの、今。」
Hold your breath, for now.”
ローリンガールの成れの果て
This is how it ends for a Rolling Girl,
届かない、向こうの色
Unable to reach the colors on the other side
重なる声と声を
The overlapping voices,
混ぜあわせて、混ぜあわせて。
They blend together, blend together
「問題ない。」と呟いた
She mutters, "I'm fine."
言葉は失われた。
but the words fail her
どうなったって良いんだってさ、
Not caring how it ends
間違いだって起こしちゃおうと誘う、坂道。
An upward climb that invites mistakes
もう一回、もう一回。
One more time, one more time
私をどうか転がしてと
Please, get me rolling
少女は言う 少女は言う
The girl said, the girl said
無口に意味を重ねながら！
With her intense silence!
「もう良いかい？」
“How about now?”
「もう少し、
“Just a little more,
もうすぐ何か見えるだろうと。
We should see something soon.
息を止めるの、今。」
Hold your breath, for now.”
もう一回、もう一回。
One more time, one more time
「私は今日も転がります。」と、
“I'll roll along again today”
少女は言う 少女は言う
The girl said, the girl said
言葉に笑みを奏でながら！
Breathing laughter into the words!
「もう良いかい？ もう良いよ。
“How about now? OK, you can look.
そろそろ君も疲れたろう、ね。」
You must be exhausted too, right?”
息を止めるの、今。
We’ll stop breathing, now.
Hold your breath, for now.
Ah...
Whoa!
Yay!
Ciao everyone!
Ciao Tittini!
Hi!
It's me, Raora Panthera
from Hololive English -Justice-
Raora!
The cat means BIG STAGE!
Oh my god, look at this!
Whoa!
Hey, what is this place?
Why are we here?
And also, what day is it?
What day is it?
Is it... is it...?
Is it my birthday?
Yay!
Thank you everyone for being here
on this special day.
I'm so happy to see everyone!
Ta-da-da-da-da!
Hi everyone!
And talking about my birthday,
I have a special hashtag for today,
which is #RaoraBDay2026!
Woo!
So everyone make sure,
if you want to share some screenshots
and you want to share some comments
on social media,
make sure to use this hashtag!
Thank you so much!
Oh, but maybe now we should take a look at...
we should take a look at this stage!
Whoo!
It's so... it's so big, isn't it?
It's a little bit like... dreamy,
seems like we are in a dream.
Maybe... maybe I'm sleeping?
Maybe I'm sleeping?
Oh...
Whoo! It's so... surrealism kind of thing.
What... what is this place?
Where am I?
Oh... whoa!
Hey? Hey?
Eh? My... my idol outfit?
What? Huh?
Why my idol outfit now?
Maybe that means I should sing more.
Well, might as well!
So please,
listen to my song!
交わした約束忘れないよ
I won't forget the promise we made.
目を閉じ確かめる
I close my eyes and confirm it.
押し寄せた闇 振り払って進むよ
I'll brush aside the encroaching
darkness and move forward.
コネクト
[Connect]
Lyrics/Music: 渡辺翔
[Lyrics/Music: Sho Watanabe]
いつになったらなくした未来を
When will I be able to see
the lost future...
私ここでまた見ることできるの?
...here again?
溢れ出した不安の影を
The shadows of anxiety
that have overflowed...
何度でも裂いて
...I will tear through again and again,
この世界歩んでこう
and walk through this world.
とめどなく刻まれた 時は今始まり告げ
Time, which has been engraved endlessly,
now signals the beginning.
変わらない思いをのせ
Carrying my unchanging feelings,
閉ざされた扉開けよう
I will open the closed door.
目覚めた心は走り出した未来を描くため
My awakened heart has started running
to draw the future.
難しい道で立ち止まっても
Even if I stop on a difficult path,
空はきれいな青さでいつも待っててくれる
the sky is always waiting with a beautiful blue.
だから怖くない
So I'm not afraid.
もう何があっても挫けない
No matter what happens, I won't be discouraged.
振り返れば仲間がいて
If I look back, I have friends,
気がつけば優しく包まれてた
and when I realize it,
I was gently wrapped up.
何もかもが歪んだ世界で
In a world where everything was distorted,
唯一信じれるここが救いだった
this, the only thing I can believe in,
was my salvation.
喜びも悲しみもわけあえば強まる想い
If we share both joy and sadness,
our feelings will grow stronger.
この声が届くのなら
If this voice reaches you,
きっと奇跡はおこせるだろう
surely a miracle can happen.
Then I can certainly create a miracle, right?
交わした約束忘れないよ
I won't forget the promise we made
目を閉じ確かめる
I'll close my eyes and ascertain it
押し寄せた闇 振り払って進むよ
Shaking off the darkness that closed in on me, I advance on
どんなに大きな壁があっても 越えてみせるからきっと
Because no matter how great of a wall there is
I'll show you I'll overcome it, so I'll certainly
明日信じて祈って
Believe in tomorrow and pray
壊れた世界で彷徨って私は
Wandering through this broken world, I...
引き寄せられるように辿り着いた
...reached it as though I was drawn towards it
目覚めた心は走り出した未来を描くため
My awoken heart has started to run
in order to draw the future
難しい道で立ち止まっても
Even if I come to a standstill on a difficult road
空はきれいな青さでいつも待っててくれる
The sky is always waiting for me in a beautiful blue
だから怖くない
So I'm not scared
もう何があっても挫けない
By now, no matter what happens, I won't get disheartened
ずっと明日待って
Forever waiting for tomorrow
Yay!
I'm so excited! Oh, happy birthday!
Thank you, Raora! Thank you!
I'm so excited for you! It's your first 3D birthday live!
It is! And look at us with our... cool outfit!
I know! We are so pretty! We are so gorgeous!
So cool! Ah, I'm so cool!
You are!
I am so cool!
And you know, because you're so cool,
I want to give you a beautiful color that I think would suit you.
Me?
Yes.
Which color? Pink? Is it going to be pink?
Um, it's... if you look at your eyes, your beautiful yellow eyes...
They... they have curiosity and playfulness.
And I think it suits you.
And so I would like to give this color, this beautiful color around us.
Which color?
Are you colorblind?
Hey! Kronii! You've been bullying me on my birthday!
You're supposed to be nice to me!
No, I mean your beautiful yellow eyes...
Ah!
It's beautiful! It's like...
Why, on my birthday, instead of giving me a gift, you come here,
you sing and dance with me, and then you just start bullying me?
You know what? Get out of here!
I complimented you!
I complimented you! Golden! Golden eyes! Is that beautiful?
So it's kind of like yellow, right?
Yeah, yeah.
So, what does it mean? Why you give me this color to me?
I... like... I just said! Curiosity and playfulness!
Stop it! Are you even listening to me?
I'm not listening!
You're not paying attention to me! You don't care about me!
My head... you talk too much! My head...
I think you should keep up your dream.
I have a question.
OK, I have an answer.
Like, I was expecting like... blue coming from you.
Oh...
Why yellow?
Why are you making me laugh?
Is it because of the yellow?
It's... it's your...
It's just this everything is so beautiful.
You're obsessed with my eyes.
Your eyes are so beautiful.
I was expecting more like a blue,
because I thought you were like... sad, and sea...
Well, you don't have a blue color scheme... oh.
But you, you are blue!
Yeah, but it's because...
I give you blue!
Oh, thank you.
What does that mean?
Loneliness? Sadness? Fear? Maybe?
Oh. That's...
Why would you give that to me?
Because...
I thought you liked me!
I like you!
You invited me all the way here...
But you're blue! I give you this beautiful color...
...and you give me blue?
Look at you! You're so pretty like blue!
I'm so... yeah.
And you're so pretty!
Stop it! No, you stop!
You know what? We can maybe blend
blue and pink together to get... purple.
Purple.
Never mind.
What does purple mean?
What does purple mean? I don't know!
We'll find out!
Oh.
Whoa, purple! You just spoiled it! Whoa!
We'll find out, I guess.
To be continued, everyone.
To be continued, everyone!
So keep watching... my, my... no, our...
That's not your birthday, it's my birthday!
It is your birthday!
It is my birthday!
So we're gonna keep watching everyone.
I'm gonna keep singing and dancing for you, okay?
Whoa! And be sure to use her hashtag, okay?
Yes! Hell yeah!
#RaoraBday2026!
Hell yeah!
Ciao ciao!
Also thank you Kronii for coming.
Oh, yeah you're welcome.
I forgot to thank you.
Yeah, thank you for having me.
Thank you for singing and dancing with me!
It was so fun!
Okay, keep up the good work!
Keep, keep the good work!
Woo! Let's go! Ciao ciao!
Brave Shine
[Title: Brave Shine]
左手に隠した
Wishes hidden in my left hand...
願いは願いのままで
...remain as they are
覚めない幻見てた
Dreaming of an endless dream
右手には空の記憶
In my right hand, memories of a shell
誰もしらない世界の果て
At the end of a world unknown to anyone
やまない雨にうたれていた
Being struck by the never-ending rain
守りたいものを守れる強さ
Strength to protect what I want to protect
それを信じられなくなる弱さ
Weakness that makes it hard to believe in it
すべてを受け入れて
Accepting everything...
未来を探す
...searching for tomorrow
Brave shine
手を伸ばせばまだ
If I reach out my hand, there's still...
Stay the night
傷だらけの夜
A night full of scars
You save my life
かざした刃の先に想いを重ねた
Layering feelings at the tip of the raised blade
祈りは時を超えて
Prayers transcend time
Your brave shine...
光ること忘れた
Forgot to shine...
青い星が残してく
...the blue star leaves behind...
消えない影見てた
...watching the unerasable shadow
Break down
崩れ落ちてゆく星座が
The crumbling constellations
傷つけ合う夜
Nights where we hurt each other
You're breaking dawn
交わした言葉の中に
In the exchanged words
一人を支えた
Supporting one another
確かな夢を添えて
Accompanied by a certain dream
守りたいものを守れるのなら
If I can protect what I want to protect
全てを受け入れて
Accepting everything
明日を探す
Searching for tomorrow
夜明けを灯す
Lighting up the dawn
Brave shine
手を伸ばせばまだ
If I reach out my hand, there's still
Stay the night
傷だらけの夜
A night full of scars
You save my life
重ねた涙の果てに
At the end of shed tears
光を見つけた
Finding light
祈りは時を超えて
Prayers transcend time
My brave shine
Woo! Happy Birthday Raora!
Happy Birthday! Tanti auguri!
Happy Birthday! Best wishes!
Shall we introduce ourselves?
Of course! Please do.
自己紹介お願いします、先輩！
Self-introductions please, seniors!
Introduction, okay! Yes, please!
こんやっぴー！ホロライブ4期生の...
Kon-yappi! Hololive 4th generation's...
オールド先輩の常闇トワ様でーす！
"Old Senpai" Tokoyami Towa-sama! Yay!
Old Senpai! Towa-senpai! ありがとう！
Old Senpai! Towa-senpai! Thank you!
え、オールド先輩か... Really? ちょっと待って！
Eh, "Old Senpai", huh... Really? Wait a minute!
Calliope is only a little bit younger than Towa-sama.
What? Okay fine. オールド先輩、森カリオペです。
What? Okay fine. "Old Senpai" Mori Calliope here.
From Hololive English -Myth-.
What's up, fellow pink? Fellow pink!
Pink is powerful!
え、トワ様、You're also pink?
Eh, Towa-sama, you're also pink?
It is pink? ですか？ピンク？
It is pink? Is it? Pink?
Of course, different shades of pink, right?
Yeah, different shades. Colors are so important.
So we must say that this is the pink team, right?
Pink team! Pink-Purple team! お願いいたします！
Pink team! Pink-Purple team! Nice to meet you!
Yes, wonderful.
But you know, the lighting actually...
...when we were singing was blue.
Yeah, was blue. So pretty, right?
What kind of emotion does the blue represent?
え、どんな感情？ブルー。
Eh, what kind of emotion? Blue.
Blue... ブルー。
Blue... Blue.
ブルーは結構寂しいとか...
Blue is quite lonely...
ちょっとそういう悲しいみたいなイメージあるけど...
...and has a bit of a sad image like that, but...
でも綺麗なイメージもあるよ。
...it also has a beautiful image.
But also beautiful. Sad, lonely, also beautiful.
For Calliope, I think sometimes maybe there's some fear.
怖さ、a little scary, right?
Fear, a little scary, right?
But, you know, emotions are beautiful, right?
感情がめっちゃ美しいと思う。
I think emotions are really beautiful.
Positive, negative, either way, colors are beautiful.
I agree with you.
Even if sometimes we have fear and we're scared...
...maybe we should overcome, we should do our best to...
怖くても頑張らないといけないね。
Even if it's scary, we have to do our best.
例えば、singing on stage together...
For example, singing on stage together...
...speaking Japanese... It's so scary!
You just gotta try your best, throw your fears away.
怖くないよ！ How do you... how do you overcome?
It's not scary! How do you... how do you overcome?
We just sang "Brave Shine"! "Brave Shine"!
We just sang. So that's a good song.
So maybe fitting? Right?
Fight your fears! 怖くないね。
Fight your fears! It's not scary.
勇気持って。 Courage.
Have courage. Courage.
And, yeah, challenge your dreams.
But fears are also part of our lives, right?
Maybe if we don't feel the fear, then how can we overcome?
Like, how can we do... how to say...
...I don't know the word... like...
How can we challenge our past self and do...
...our best every single day, right?
怖くなかったら、まあ、チャレンジじゃないよね。
If it's not scary, well, it's not a challenge, is it?
確かにね。怖かったらもっと...
Certainly. If it's scary, even more...
強くなれると思う
I think you can become stronger
You can become stronger if it's scary.
Yeah!
かっこいいね
That's cool.
うわー! ありがとうございます!
Whoa! Thank you so much!
ラオーラ 意味深
Raora, that's deep.
Whoa, deep meaning.
That's cool.
かっこいいね
Cute and cool, Raora.
ラオーラならできる!
You can do it, Raora!
You are cool.
Everyone, everyone here's cool.
みんなクール
Everyone's cool.
Team Pink is very cool.
Pink's a cool color, okay? Hey!
Well, happy birthday to you.
Thank you so much, Mori!
本当におめでとう!
Congratulations, truly!
おめでとう!
Happy birthday!
Thank you so much for singing Break Spell with me.
It's a very meaningful song, and I really appreciate to have my...
大先輩s with me. Thank you so much!
great senpais with me. Thank you so much!
Yeah, the old senpais.
Old senpais here with you.
Well, myself and Towa got to get out of here...
...but Raora, you keep on keeping on, okay?
Okay!
I'll do my best then!
And we'll see you guys later, okay?
See you guys later!
Bye everybody!
Bye bye!
Peace!
約束 / Lyrics, Music: Eve
[Song: Promise / Lyrics, Music: Eve]
知らない世界の中では
In a world I don't know
時間が止まっていくような気がした
It felt as if time was coming to a stop
いつも見せないような表情が
Expressions you wouldn't usually show
その距離が少しだけ愛おしかった
That distance was just a little bit precious
巻き戻せないと
Saying we can't turn back time
はしゃいでいるその横顔を抱きかかえて
I embrace your profile as you frolic
闇をじっと駆け出した
And dashed straight through the darkness
君に染まる世界が
A world colored by you
かじかんだ両手が心から願うよ
My frozen hands pray from the bottom of my heart
終わらせたくなどないんだと
That I don't want this to ever end
思い出の中にはいつも君の姿
You are always there in my memories
夢のまま 覚めないまま
Remaining a dream, without ever waking up
その笑顔が忘れられないよ
I can't forget that smile of yours
言葉では足りないようで 大人になんてなれないよ
Words aren't enough, I can't even become an adult
くだらないことばっかり それでも楽しかった
Just trivial things, but even so, it was fun
ずっと今がこのまま続いたらいいななんて
Wishing that 'now' would just continue like this forever
左に跳ね返してみせるの
I'll show you I can bounce it back to the left
泣きそうな声で
With a voice that sounds like it's about to cry
新しい世界では
In the new world
きっと心から笑えていけるかな
I wonder if I'll be able to laugh from my heart
謝りたいな
I want to apologize
見せる顔なんてないよ
I don't have a face to show you
僕は君のもう未来などどこにもいないようだ
It seems I'm no longer anywhere in your future
逃げ出したくないよ
I don't want to run away
あの日に戻りたくなるよ
It makes me want to go back to that day
振り向いてばかりの現在ならば 諦めよう
If the present is just about looking back, let's give up
抱ききれない祈りも
Prayers I can't fully embrace
確かめたい気持ちも
Feelings I want to confirm
今なら言えるだろうか
I wonder if I can say it now
終わらせたくはないんだと知って
Knowing that I don't want it to end
何度でも言うよ 景色は儚げに
I'll say it as many times as it takes, the scenery is fleeting
足元はおぼつかない 気づけば走り出していたんだ
My footing is unsteady, before I knew it I was running
何度でも言うよ 会いたい言葉など
I'll say it as many times as it takes, words like 'I miss you'
見つかるわけでもない それでもただ信じてみたいから
Can't be found, but even so I just want to try and believe
思い出の中 君の姿
In my memories, your figure
夢のまま 覚めないまま
Remaining a dream, without waking up
変わらないな
It doesn't change, does it
思い出の中にはいつも君の姿
You are always there in my memories
夢のまま 覚めないまま
Remaining a dream, without waking up
その笑顔が忘れられないよ
I can't forget that smile of yours
言葉では足りないようで 大人になんてなれないよ
Words aren't enough, I can't even become an adult
くだらないことばっかり それでも楽しかった
Just trivial things, but even so, it was fun
ずっと今がこのまま続いたらいいね
I wish this moment would last forever
今度は僕から掴んでみせるよ
Next time, I'll be the one to grab hold
約束しよう
Let's make a promise
約束をしよう
The Everlasting Guilty Crown
Lyrics, Music: ryo (supercell)
[Song: The Everlasting Guilty Crown]
[Lyrics, Music: ryo (supercell)]
世界は終わりを告げようとしてる
The world is trying to proclaim its end,
誰にももう止められはしない
And no one has been able to stop that.
———始まる
It begins...
崩壊のシンフォニーが鳴り響いて
A symphony of destruction resounds everywhere,
降る雨はまるで涙の音色
And the falling raindrops are like the sound of the tears.
教えて
Tell me:
支配し支配され人たちは
The people, who govern and who is being governed,
いつかその心に憎しみを
One day hatred will settle in their hearts,
そして愛することを思い出せず
And then, not remembering what it means to love,
争うの？
They will attack each other?
この歌が聴こえてる
I hear this song!
命あるすべてのものよ
You, all living beings,
真実はあなたの胸の中にある
The truth is in your hearts,
嵐の海を行くときも
Because, even when you’re sailing through a stormy sea,
決して臆することのない強さを
It gives you the strength not to be afraid of anything,
くれるから
Because it will give it to you.
けれども進むほど風は強い
However the further we go, the stronger the wind becomes,
希望の火はやがて消えていく
And now the flame of hope begins to fade.
「明かりをよこせ」と奪い合い
“Give the light to me!” — people start taking it away,
果てに人は殺し合う
And in the end they just kill each other...
涙などとうに枯れて
And their tears have long dried up.
気づいて
Understand:
その目は互いを認めるため
The eyes are given to us, to notice each other.
その声は想いを伝えるため
The voice is given to us, to convey our feelings.
その手は大事な人と繋ぐためにある
The hands are given to us, to bind ourselves to those who are dear to us.
この歌が聴こえてる
I hear this song!
世界中の寄る辺なきものよ
You, who are abandoned by everyone in this world,
希望はあなたの胸の中にある
The hope lives in your hearts,
燃え盛る炎の中でも
Because, even when you’re in a blazing flame,
決して傷つくことのない強さを
It gives you the strength not to get hurt by anything,
くれるから
Because it will give it to you.
その手で守ろうとしたものは
What you’re trying to protect with your hands,
愛するものだったのだろうか
Are the ones you really love, aren’t they?
赤く染まったその手を眺めて
After looking at these hands painted scarlet,
やっと自らがしてきた愚かさを
You finally realize the stupidity of your own actions,
過ちと認めるその罪を
That sin that you admit is your mistake,
止めどなく溢れるその涙を知る
And you come to know those uncontrollable, overflowing tears.
この歌が聴こえてる
If you can hear this song,
生命ある全ての者よ
it's for you, each and every one of you,
真実はあなたの
The truth is...
胸の中にある
...inside you all.
嵐の海は静まった
The ocean's storms have quieted,
失ったものは数えきれなくとも
but we've lost more people than we can count.
この歌が聴こえてる
If you can hear this song,
世界中の寄る辺なき者よ
if you have nowhere to go,
希望はあなたの
Hope is...
胸の中にある
...inside you all.
悲しみの夜を超える時
Even if we're past the night of sadness,
必ずあなたは生きていく強さを
you will get the strength to live on,
持てるから
because you can.
SECURITY BREACH / HELLO, READER. I AM...
[Visual Text: SECURITY BREACH / HELLO, READER. I AM...]
ENCRYPTED MESSAGE DECODED. MESSAGE: "HELLO..."
[Visual Text: ENCRYPTED MESSAGE DECODED. MESSAGE: "HELLO..."]
Ahhhh! We did it!
Yeeeeeey!
Frtiti! Fluffy Tail!
Frtiti! Oh! Look at our tail!
Whoa!
Whoa, sway!
One, two... Whoa!
Which one is longer?
Mine is longer!
Happy Birthday, Raora!
Yeeey! Thank you!
Thank you for being here! Look at her! Look at her!
You should introduce yourself first!
Oh! Hi!
Who are you? Who is this mysterious creature?
How many ears do you have? I'm a mysterious creature!
One, two, three, four...
Four?
Five, six, seven...
It's four! Six, seven ears!
Oh, geez! Who are you? Introduce yourself!
Hello! Hi Chatini! Hi, I'm Jieriku! And I am a four-eared fox!
And self-proclaimed best friend of Birthday Girl over here! Hi!
She loves me very much, doesn't she?
I love her very much! Yeah!
Yeah, thank you so much for being here today!
Thank you for having me! It was so nice to dance with you!
I have come here today to bring you...
Yes?
...a lot of passion and determination!
That you need to unleash when you do your beautiful art every single day!
I will be very passionate from now on!
I need you to unleash it now! I can't wait any longer!
I've been waiting this whole time! Give me a bite! Give me a dab!
Give me an anything! Just do it!
Unleash it! Unleash the demon! The passion!
Sorry guys, I have to go now!
Thank you so much for watching!
No, no, no! Not that fast! Not that fast!
You will continue... you will continue my life!
No, no, no, no!
Thank you so much everyone! I'm gonna leave you!
No she won't! Don't leave me!
I'm gonna leave you! Do not!
Do you know the dance for the next song?
It's gonna be very fun, you should...
You want me to join?
Yeah, yeah! No, no, you HAVE to do it live now!
That's why!
I have to do it live now? Alright! I'm ready!
Okay! Show me! Show me!
You said you took the... Whoa!
Yes! Yes! Unleash the determination! Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes!
Yeah! And now, Birthday Girl time!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Hey! I saw that! I saw that!
You can... I saw that!
Did you see that? Cause I saw it!
Ah, you didn't see it!
I saw it! You should see it from the stage!
We have been to... together! You saw it every day!
You don't have to see anything else!
God, you're so violent! That's good! That's good!
The determination is coming out! The passion is...
Oh, the passion! I'll be passionate! The passion, please!
I'm egg-maxing, please! Relax!
Sorry, sorry! I can't do that!
Oh, come here, come here grandma, come here!
Ah, this is okay!
She wants to talk. She definitely wants to talk.
I want to talk!
What do I want to talk about?
I said you WANT to talk.
I want to talk! You called me grandma, how freaking dare you!
How freaking dare you!
Why are you... Why are you self-proclaiming yourself all these moves...
...and pulling out, you know, all the crazy dance?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, right!
It was such a tough dance, wasn't it?
Oh, it was so hard!
She's gonna treat me for dinner to celebrate her birthday!
Yeah! It's my birthday!
Yes, yes, yes! Wait, you should...
...You should treat me for dinner!
What are you gonna get for me, Birthday Girl?
Actually...
Yes?
What are YOU gonna get for me?
Oh my god, point taken!
No, no, no, no!
Oh yeah, because you guys know...
Don't look at the camera! Not this part! No!
Wait! Wait! Before starting she said,
"I am so nervous!"
No, I didn't!
She said, "I'm so nervous, when I'm done..."
"...I'm gonna give you 10 dollars!"
Absolutely not!
Yeah, thank you, Raora!
That hasn't happened! What? Thank you?
Nooooooo!
Thank you, thank you!
It's over... ah...
You know my data for the payment, okay?
Hey, come back!
I don't want to send you money anymore!
Oh yeah, you gotta.
You owe me 40 pounds already, mate. Front taxes, okay?
She's so in debt with me! And she takes...
This is really bad of you!
It's my birthday, I decide what I want, I decide everything!
And if I want 10 dollars, you're gonna give me 10 dollars!
What should I do? The drama...
Chatini, please tell her!
Chatini, tell her to give me the 10 dollars!
You look so determined! You really want this money...
Fine!
Here it is! Just buy yourself some cannoli or something!
I'm over it! I'm so done! Live on stream!
Oh my god, it's over.
The mortgage... the car... the insurance...
It's okay, it's okay!
Don't talk about negative things now!
Because today is my birthday! We gotta celebrate!
Did you bring cake for us?
Ah... yes!
Where is it? Actually? The cake?
I... I can't tell right now...
Cake! Cake! Cake! Cake!
It's in the drawing! It's in the drawing!
Ah! No! Don't touch my tail!
Hey, hey! I grabbed your tail!
Come here!
No! No! No! Don't touch!
It's kind of easy to grab, it's very long.
Listen, listen! You need to walk,
you need to run way faster if you want me to do more...
No, no, no!
Oh you know what? Then I'll grab yours!
Here it comes! You cannot... it's her!
It's her! I'm grabbing her!
Taking a bite? Meret?
Ah! Meret! Just don't...
Oh, what are we doing now?
And she's not gonna be happy with this...
You know what? I'm gonna go and talk to your manager by myself!
No, you cannot talk to my manager!
I'll talk to my manager!
I'm so done! I'm done!
Now you're not...
Okay, actually we're done.
That was a great workout!
We really did deserve cake after all.
Haha, we deserve cake after all, isn't it?
What's your favorite flavor?
My favorite flavor is...
RICOTTA!
Okay, we have to go now! We have to go!
There's more to come! There's so much more!
She has so many surprises for you!
You were the surprise!
Am I? Am I not?
But I have more surprises!
She does, she does, she does!
So thank you so much! Happy Birthday Raora!
Rico!
Yippee!
Rico! Thank you for having me here!
Pink creature! Pink creature!
Big grey creature!
Oh yes!
Actually talking about colors, you should put some colors on!
Well, I bought some new glasses, they're nice and red,
you should see them, I'll show you sometime soon!
Ahhh! Yippee!
Let's go!
More songs!
More songs to come! Happy Birthday!
Yeah! Thank you, Rico!
Hi Chatini!
Okay then, ta-ta!
Bye-bye!
Bye!
言って。
Lyrics, Music: n-buna
[Song: Say it.
Lyrics, Music: n-buna]
あのね、
You see,
私 実は気付いてるの
I’ve actually realized already
ほら、君がいったこと
Look, about that thing you said
あまり
I didn’t feel like
考えたいと思えなくて
thinking about it too much
忘れてたんだけど
So I had forgotten about it, but
盲目的に盲動的に妄想的に生きて
Living blindly, recklessly, delusionally
衝動的な焦燥的な消極的なままじゃ駄目だったんだ
Impulsively, impatiently, negatively didn’t do me any good
きっと、人生最後の日を前に思うのだろう
I bet, when I face the last day of my life, it’ll come to mind.
全部、全部言い足りなくて惜しいけど
It’s a pity that I can’t say enough about everything, but—
あぁ、
Ah,
いつか人生最後の日、君がいないことを
on the last day of my life, you won’t be here.
もっと、もっと、もっと、もっと、
More, more, more, more,
ちゃんと 言って
say it clearly.
あのね、空が青いのってどうやって伝えればいいんだろうね
You know, when the sky is blue, I wonder how I can share it.
夜の雲が高いのってどうすれば君もわかるんだろう
And when the night clouds are high, I wonder how I can let you know that.
言って
Say it.
あのね、私実はわかってるの
You know, I actually know now...
もう君が逝ったこと
that you’re already dead.
あのね、わからず屋って言うんだろうね
You know, well, you would say I’m being stubborn.
忘れたいんだけど
I want to forget, but—
もっとちゃんと言ってよ 忘れないようメモにしてよ
Say it more clearly. Make a note to remind me.
明日十時にホームで待ち合わせとかしよう
Let’s make plans, like meeting at the platform tomorrow at ten.
牡丹は散っても花だ
A scattered peony is still a showy flower.
夏が去っても追慕は切だ
The summer is over but still missed so much.
口に出して 声に出して 君が言って
Speak out, say it out loud. I want you to say it.
そして人生最後の日、君が見えるのなら
And on the last day of my life, if I can see you,
きっと、人生最後の日も愛をうたうのだろう
I bet, on the last day of my life, I’ll sing love as always.
全部、全部無駄じゃなかったって言うから
It wasn’t all for nothing, you say, so—
あぁ、いつか人生最後の日、君がいないことがまだ信じられないけど
Ah, on the last day of my life, I still can’t believe that you won’t be here, but—
もっと、もっと、もっと、もっと、もっと、もっと、もっと、君が
More, more, more, more, more, more, more, you say it,
もっと、もっと、もっと、もっと、もっと、もっと、もっと、もっと、
more, more, more, more, more, more, more, more,
もっと、ちゃんと言って
more clearly, say it.
Thank you so much for being here!
Mio-senpai, Okayu-senpai!
I can't believe we sang together!
It was so fun!
Thank you, thank you!
ゲストは、ミオ先輩とおかゆ先輩です！
Our guests are Mio-senpai and Okayu-senpai!
ラオラ、ハッピーバースデー！
Raora, Happy Birthday!
ありがとうございます！ ありがとう！
Thank you so much! Thank you!
来てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming!
自己紹介、お願いします！
Please introduce yourselves!
うち、うち、うちだよ！ 狼ミオだよ！ ホロライブゲーマーズの狼ミオです！
It's me, me, me! I'm Ookami Mio! I'm Ookami Mio from Hololive Gamers!
かわいい～！
So cute~!
はーい！ もぐもぐ～おかゆー！ ホロライブゲーマーズの猫又おかゆです！
Yes! Mogu mogu Okayu! I'm Nekomata Okayu from Hololive Gamers!
もぐもぐもぐもぐ... I'm gonna eat you! もぐもぐもぐもぐ...
Mogu mogu mogu mogu... I'm gonna eat you! Mogu mogu mogu mogu...
ヤムヤム！ ヤムヤム！
Yum yum! Yum yum!
Thank you so much! ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much! Thank you!
よし、行くぞ！ ミオズ・イングリッシュ・チャレンジ！
Alright, here we go! Mio's English Challenge!
Hey, the brow, right?
Everything in the concert was beautiful, wasn't it?
Yeah, it was! It was really beautiful!
Okayuzu English Challenge!
Okayu's English Challenge!
Cyan symbolizes sincerity and self-acceptance.
You don't have to try to be strong...
...or try to be perfect.
Just accept yourself as you are...
...and go with the flow, and you'll be fine.
Can I be strong?
Strong cat! Strong cat!
I wanna be a strong big cat!
Big cat! Yay!
Raora strong cat!
Thank you senpais for your nice words. Thank you!
Thank you! Thank you!
心に響きました
It resonated in my heart.
良かったわ。良かった良かった。
I'm glad. That's great.
Then, from here...
...I've got some exciting news for you guys!
It's about Raora Panthera Birthday Celebration 2026!
So please senpai help me out, okay?
Okay!
グッズ紹介、お手伝いします！
We'll help with the merch intro!
任せて！
Leave it to us!
Okay, so, Raora Panthera Birthday Anniversary 2026!
Goods are now on sale!
Okay, okay, let's go, let's go!
Let's go!
Take a look here!
こちらどうぞ！
Here you go!
Whoa! Wow!
So gorgeous! Look at this illustration, I like it!
好き！
I love it!
すごーい、かわいい！
Wow, so cute!
みんなかわいいよ！
Everyone is so cute!
The illustration was drawn by Komiya-sensei!
Thank you so much for making this beautiful art! I'm so happy!
胡宮先生に描いてもらったみたいですね。
It seems Komiya-sensei drew this for us.
ライブのRaoraをテーマに描いてもらったみたいですね。
It looks like she drew it with 'Live Raora' as the theme.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
Okay, so let's take a closer look at the details!
First up, this one!
Whoa!
B-Day Live Long T-shirt!
ロンTシャツ！
Long T-shirt!
It features a motif logo on the back...
...and there's also design on the sleeves...
...so it's really, really cool for everyday life! So please check it out!
かわいい！ロゴとかも付いててね...
Cute! It has a logo and everything...
...いっぱいデザインが凝っててかわいい！
...the design is so detailed and cute!
ねー、すごいすごい！
Right? Amazing, amazing!
And next, we have... Ta-da!
Body bag!
ボディバッグ！
And it's a bag designed for everyday use...
...that lets you show off your love for Big Cat!
Big Cat! Big Cat! Big Cat!
ラオーラ推しアピールできる、普段使いできるバッグになっております！
It's a bag for everyday use where you can show you're a Raora fan!
素晴らしい！ありがとう！
Wonderful! Thank you!
Next up is... Ta-da!
Cry, Cry Chattini!
おしおきチャッティーニ！
Punished Chattini!
Chattini! Doshita no Chattini?
Chattini! What's wrong, Chattini?
That's what you deserve! That's what you get!
Sorry, sorry! That's what you get!
まあまあまあ...
Now, now...
Crying Chattini, that comes with an amazing pouch!
Next please! Next please!
Ta-da!
Kawaii!
Perfect! You can combine them together! So good!
チャッティーニが洗濯機の中に閉じ込められちゃったみたいです！
It looks like Chattini got trapped inside the washing machine!
Wash wash Chattini!
ぐるぐる、ぐるぐる！
Spin spin, spin spin!
はい、こちら、チャッティーニが閉じ込められてるのは、ぬいぐるみ用のマルチポーチですね。
Yes, this one where Chattini is trapped is a multi-pouch for plushies.
すごいかわいい！
So cute!
And next up is... Ta-da! Voice Pack!
It's gonna be fun to listen to it, so please check it out!
ラオーラがね、頑張って収録したボイス聞いてみてくださいね、皆さんね。
Everyone, please listen to the voice that Raora worked hard to record.
お願いします！
Please!
And there is also bonus for purchasing all the full set.
And here it is!
Whoa!
Cheki-style photo with hand-written message signed!
お、こちらは直筆サイン入りのチェキ風ブロマイドカードがフルセットについてきます
Oh, this is an autographed cheki-style bromide
card that comes with the full set.
イェー、すごーい！
Yeah, amazing!
And cheki-style bro... bromide... English 難しい！
And cheki-style bro... bromide... English is hard!
English 難しかった！
English was difficult!
難しい！ディフィカルト・イングリッシュ！
Difficult! Difficult English!
With foil-stamped repro... repro... repro...
I can't talk anymore! Signature! Whoo!
ちなみにサインは数量限定となっております
By the way, the signature version is
limited in quantity.
はい、お願いします！お願いします！
Yes, please! Please!
So here's the full set again, so please go check it out everyone! Thank you, thank you!
So here's the full set again, so please go check
it out everyone! Thank you, thank you!
And that was the merch lineup for Raora Panthera's Birthday Celebration 2026! Thank you so much!
And that was the merch lineup for Raora Panthera's
Birthday Celebration 2026! Thank you so much!
ミオ先輩、おかゆ先輩、Thank you so much for your support! Thank you so much!
Mio-senpai, Okayu-senpai, thank you so much
for your support! Thank you so much!
こちらこそ！お疲れ様！
Our pleasure! Good job!
上手くフォロー出来てたかな？
I wonder if I was able to follow along well.
どうかな？
I wonder.
出来てたかな？
I wonder if I did.
Thank you!
でも凄く楽しかったです！
But it was really fun!
Yes, yes, 凄くハッピー！
Yes, yes, I'm very happy!
楽しかった！
It was fun!
ありがとう、嬉しい！
Thank you, I'm so happy!
Alright, now the merch announcement is done...
The next song will be the last one. 最後！
The next song will be the last one. The end!
Last one! 最後！
Last one! The end!
Last song! Whoo!
楽しみ！
Looking forward to it!
I'm kind of nervous... push for me okay, senpais?
I'm kind of nervous... support me okay, senpais?
オッケー、オッケー！頑張れ、頑張れ！
Okay, okay! Do your best!
頑張れ、ラオーラ！ファイト、ラオーラ！
Go for it, Raora! Fight, Raora!
ありがとう！じゃあ、バイバイ！Let's say goodbye!
Thank you! Well then, bye-bye! Let's say goodbye!
オッケー！
Okay!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
Draw.
Lyrics, Music Arrangement: OrcaNyan
[Title: Draw.]
[Lyrics, Music Arrangement: OrcaNyan]
夢のぬくもりと
With the warmth of a dream
指先に絵の具の匂い
The scent of paint on my fingertips
湿ったキャンバスの上には
On the damp canvas
まだ知らない色が息をする
Colors I don't know yet breathe
All the pieces I picked up
Unravel in my own chest
“It's okay,” I whisper softly
Saving it back to myself
迷いも震えも
Both hesitation and trembling
隠さなくていいから
You don't have to hide them
この線の全部が私へ続く
All these lines lead to me
I'm drawing out my true color
滲んだ輪郭も
Even the blurred outlines
淡く、脆く、煌めいて
Faintly, fragilely, sparkling
形になってゆくの
They are taking shape
夜明けの面影に
In the trace of dawn
集めた色を重ね
Layering the gathered colors
Draw it slow, draw it true
夜明けの夢現
The half-asleep state at dawn
微睡みに余白の答え
The answer in the blank space of a slumber
白いページに色が咲いていく
Colors bloom on white pages
息づいた景色を描き出す
Drawing out a landscape that has come to life
All the colors I held back
Start to gather in the hush
“It's all right,” the first light tells me
Sending warmth into my heart
願いも希望も
Both wishes and hopes
隠さなくていいんだよ
You don't have to hide them
ほら、ありのままの私を描く
See, I'm drawing my true self
Draw.
[Song: Draw.]
At last, hold my true colors
ほどけた輪郭も
Even the untied outline
そっと、ずっと、重なって
Slowly, always, layering
私の形になる
Becoming my shape
静かな始まりに
At the quiet beginning
目覚めた色を抱いて
Holding the color that awakened
I'm drawing out my true color
滲んだ輪郭も
Even the blurred outline
淡く、脆く、煌めいて
Faintly, fragilely, sparkling
形になってゆくの
It starts taking shape
夜明けの面影を
The traces of dawn
集めた色で描く
I draw with the colors I've gathered
Draw it slow
Draw it slow, draw it true
夢のぬくもりと
With the warmth of dreams
指先に絵の具の匂い
And the scent of paint on my fingertips
ありふれた朝の先には
Beyond the ordinary morning
まだ知らない色が溢れてる
Colors I don't yet know are overflowing
ラオ～！
Raooo!
チャオ、皆さん！まだここにいますよ。
Ciao everyone, I'm still here.
私の初めてのバースデーライブを見てくれて
I just wanted to say thank you so, so much
本当に、本当にありがとうございました！
for watching my first ever birthday live.
とても楽しかったですし、皆さんも楽しんでいただけたなら嬉しいです。
I had so much fun and I hope you had so much fun too.
一生懸命頑張ったので、今とても幸せです。
I worked really, really hard and I'm so happy right now.
チャティーニのみんな、見てくれてありがとう！
So thank you Chatini, thank you everyone for watching.
見てくれて、ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!
さあ、もう行かなくちゃ。バイバイ！
Ciao, I have to go now. Bye bye!
そして忘れないで、大きな猫は…
And remember, big cat means...
大変なことになるって！
BIG TROUBLE!
ラオ～！
Raooo!
チャオ、皆さん！最後にメッセージがあります。
Ciao everyone, I have one last message for you all.
この後すぐのMVプレミアをぜひチェックしてくださいね。
Be sure to check out the MV premiere right after this.
それと、私の新しいオリジナル曲が5月11日の深夜に…
And also, my new original song will be releasing
皆さんの地域の時間で配信されます！
on all platforms on May 11th, midnight...
見逃さないでくださいね、いいですか？
...in your local timezone. So don't miss it, okay?
グッズもチェックしてね！バイバイバイ！
Also go check out my merch! Bye-bye-bye!
ラオ～！バイバイ！
Raooo! Bye bye!
チャティーニのみんな、愛とサポートをありがとう！
ずっと一緒だよ！！
Thank you to all my Chatini for the love and support!
TOGETHER FOREVER!!